[
    {
        "question": "What symbol is used to symbolise percentage?",
        "options": [
            "=",
            "%",
            "!",
            "/"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "%"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sum of 18 \u2013 9?",
        "options": [
            "10",
            "8",
            "9",
            "2"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many sides does a pentagon have?",
        "options": [
            "3",
            "4",
            "5",
            "6"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the product of 7 x 7?",
        "options": [
            "25",
            "77",
            "11",
            "49"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the answer of 100\u00f7 50?",
        "options": [
            "2",
            "3",
            "10",
            "5"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is one half written as a fraction?",
        "options": [
            "1/2",
            "2",
            "2/1",
            "2/3"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "1/2"
    },
    {
        "question": "If the time is 12pm, how many hours is it until 6pm?",
        "options": [
            "4",
            "6",
            "18",
            "12"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many metres are in a kilometre?",
        "options": [
            "10",
            "100",
            "1000",
            "10000"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "1000"
    },
    {
        "question": "3,6,9,12,__? What is the next number in the sequence?",
        "options": [
            "16",
            "15",
            "14",
            "9"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 > 5. True or false?",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "None",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many degrees is a right angle?",
        "options": [
            "60\u00b0",
            "180\u00b0",
            "90\u00b0",
            "360\u00b0"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "90\u00b0"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many faces does a cube have?",
        "options": [
            "6",
            "8",
            "3",
            "12"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is half of one half?",
        "options": [
            "0.2",
            "1/2",
            "1/4",
            "3/2"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "1/4"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the answer of 121 \u00f7 11?",
        "options": [
            "23",
            "15",
            "11",
            "14"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "If a pizza has a diameter of 12 inches, what is its radius?",
        "options": [
            "4",
            "3",
            "12",
            "6"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the square root of 1?",
        "options": [
            "1",
            "2",
            "-1",
            "0"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the answer of 888 \u00f7 8?",
        "options": [
            "11",
            "121",
            "111",
            "100"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the answer of 15 x 15?",
        "options": [
            "25",
            "125",
            "625",
            "225"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "225"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many seconds are there in 5 minutes?",
        "options": [
            "320s",
            "60s",
            "300s",
            "30s"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "300s"
    },
    {
        "question": "What theorem is used to find the length of an unknown side and the angle of a triangle?",
        "options": [
            "Heron's theorem",
            "Euclid theorem",
            "Pythagoras theorem",
            "Triangle theorem"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Pythagoras theorem"
    },
    {
        "question": "Find average of (12,12,6)",
        "options": [
            "3",
            "12",
            "11",
            "10"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the root of 4 ?",
        "options": [
            "2",
            "4",
            "1",
            "-2"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is root of 3 ?",
        "options": [
            "Integer",
            "zero",
            "Natural",
            "Irrational"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Irrational"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the condition for even numbers?",
        "options": [
            "divisible by 2",
            "divisible by 4",
            "divisible by 1",
            " divisible by 3"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "divisible by 2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is not a fraction ?",
        "options": [
            "24/13",
            "26/1",
            "1/12",
            "32/29"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "26/1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What represents 3 slice of a 12 slice pizza ?",
        "options": [
            "1/3",
            "12/3",
            "1/4",
            "0.29"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "1/4"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many radians in 180\u00b0?",
        "options": [
            "\u03c0/\u03c0",
            "2\u03c0",
            "\u03c0/2",
            "\u03c0"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "\u03c0"
    },
    {
        "question": "\u03c0 is of which type of number?",
        "options": [
            "Rational",
            "Real",
            "Integer",
            "None"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Real"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is mean ?",
        "options": [
            "Average",
            "Mode",
            "Median",
            "Max"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Average"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is answer of 25*15",
        "options": [
            "75",
            "375",
            "625",
            "555"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "375"
    }
]